export let hardQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Where did Michael attack and kill Annie Brackett when she was trying to go see her boyfriend, Paul, in 'Halloween' (1978)?",
        answer1: "A) In her car",
        answer2: "B) In her front yard",
        answer3: "C) In her house",
        answer4: "D) At a party",
        correctAnswer: 1

    },
    {
        question: "In 'Halloween II' (1981), what medical instrument did Michael use to kill Dr. Mixter?",
        answer1: "A) He was decapitated with a bone saw.",
        answer2: "B) He was strangled with an IV tube.",
        answer3: "C) His throat was slit with a scalpel.",
        answer4: "D) He was stabbed in his eye with a syringe.",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How did Nurse Karen Bailey meet her demise in 'Halloween II' (1981)?",
        answer1: "A) She was stabbed in her chest with a butcher knife.",
        answer2: "B) She was thrown from a second storey window.",
        answer3: "C) She was beaten with a bat.",
        answer4: "D) She was scalded/drowned in the hospital's whirlpool.",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "In 'Halloween: Resurrection' (2002), how did aspiring chef Rudy Grimes lose his kitchen battle with Michael?",
        answer1: "A) He was beaten with a cutting board.",
        answer2: "B) His head was slammed repeatedly in the refrigerator door.",
        answer3: "C) He was stabbed in the neck with a corkscrew.",
        answer4: "D) He had knives shoved through his chest, pinning him to a door.",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How was John Strode taken care of in 'Halloween: The Curse of Michael Myers' (1995)?",
        answer1: "A) He was hacked repeatedly with a hatchet.",
        answer2: "B) He was stabbed, pinned to a fuse box, and electrocuted.",
        answer3: "C) He was stabbed in forehead with a butcher knife.",
        answer4: "D) His head was crushed with a sledgehammer.",
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who played Laurie Strode?",
        answer1: "A) Jamie Lee Curtis",
        answer2: "B) Florence Henderson",
        answer3: "C) Valerie Bertinelli",
        answer4: "D) Julia Roberts",
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How did Nurse How many friends did Laurie have? Bailey meet her demise in 'Halloween II' (1981)?",
        answer1: "A) Three",
        answer2: "B) Two",
        answer3: "C) One",
        answer4: "D) Five",
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What character's mask was Michael's mask made out of?",
        answer1: "A) Norman Bates from Psycho",
        answer2: "B) The blob",
        answer3: "C) The creature from the black lagoon",
        answer4: "D) Captain Kirk from Star Trek",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "In what city did Laurie live?",
        answer1: "A) Bayview",
        answer2: "B) Pittsburgh",
        answer3: "C) Haddonfield",
        answer4: "D) Memorial",
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What actor played the role of Samuel Loomis?",
        answer1: "A) David Cassidy",
        answer2: "B) Patrick Duffy",
        answer3: "C) Alfred Hitchcock",
        answer4: "D) Donald Pleasence",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "In what body part did Michael stab Laurie, near the end of the movie?",
        answer1: "A) Neck",
        answer2: "B) Hand",
        answer3: "C) Arm/Shoulder",
        answer4: "D) leg",
        correctAnswer: 3
    }
];